迈克 · 诺斯: 我还想给你们看看这个测试。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: I want to also
show you this test here.
因此，您可以为类型编写测试。
So you can write tests for types.
微软有一个叫做 dtslint 的库，它使用了 tslint。
Microsoft has a library called dtslint,
which uses tslint.
它基本上解析了链接错误消息
And it basically parses
the linting error messages and
将它们与你可以在类型中留下的特殊注释进行比较。
compares them against special comments
that you can leave in your types.
所以，这不是真的，当我说这是摩卡测试的时候，我有点撒谎了。
So, this isn't actually, I kind of
lied when I said it was a Mocha test.
这只是一个带有特殊注释的打字稿文件。
This is just a TypeScript file
with special comments in there.
这基本上断言，如果有错误,
And this basically asserts
that if there is an error,
这里一定有什么错误，我可以很容易地说,
there must be an error here,
I could just as easily say,
预期输入，迈克 · 诺斯: 错，对吗？
$ExpectType,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: False, right?
您可以围绕纯类型的事物编写测试用例。
You can write test cases around
things that are purely types.
很多人都没有意识到这一点
A lot of people don't realize this and
他们只是完全跳过测试，当它涉及到接口和诸如此类的东西。
they just skip tests completely when it
comes to interfaces and things like that.
但是，这可能是代码中一个非常棘手的区域。
But this can be a gnarly
area of your code.
如果你有一些有点抽象的东西，你真的想要有
Where if you have something that's a
little bit abstract, you really wanna have
对于变化的一些信心是非破坏性的。
some confidence around
changes being nondestructive.
所以 dtslint 就是我们要找的东西。
So dtslint is what to look for.